

Details

Josif Josifovski 20-1/5 Resen, 7310 North Macedonnia +38977919236 daniela.pavlovska@outlook.com

NATIONALITY

Macedonian

DRIVING LICENSE

Yes

06/12/1994

Skills

Time Management

Communication Skills

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Ability to Multitask

Teamwork

Leadership

Computer Skills

Customer Relations

HTML/CSS

Adobe Photoshop

Detail-oriented

Marketing Research

Initiative and Problem-solving Abilities

Profile

Experienced and self-motivated person with a responsible approach to any task I undertake or every presented situation. A strong leader with the ability to increase sales and develop strategies to retain customers. Dedicated, hardworking, and proactive, key team member with strong ability to work under pressure. Strong organizational abilities with proven successes. Loves working with people and meeting new people.

Employment History

Operator, DELTABET (MOZZARTBET), Resen

SEPTEMBER 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2022

- Managed and evaluated workflow and productivity, making changes where necessary.
- · Worked to support sales teams and rise against competition.
- · Worked well with colleagues to ensure optimal productivity.
- Built long-term trusting relationships with clients to achieve ultimate client retention.
- Provided customers with optimal customer service and excellent assistance at all times.
- · Effectively built and maintained long-lasting client relationships.
- · Delegated tasks to team members.
- · Worked well independently and also with others.

Front-end internship, ROYAL WEB LAB, Resen

JANUARY 2017 - JUNE 2017

- Helped to achieve a consistent look and visual theme across the website by promoting uniform fonts, formatting, images, and layout.
- Creating front-end code (HTML, CSS, JAVAscript) for website look.
- Uploaded final images to private web galleries for client use and enjoyment.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Communications Engineering (BSc CSCE), FICT (Faculty of Information and Communication Technologies), Bitola

SEPTEMBER 2013 - JUNE 2019

High school, SOU Car Samoil, Reesen

SEPTEMBER 2009 - MAY 2013

Languages

Macedonian (Native Proficiency)

English (Full Professional Proficiency)

Spanish (Limited Working Proficiency)